Guide to the Warwick Baker O'Neill Records, 1931-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Account Files, 1973-2001 and undated, (75 boxes)
  - Restricted Files
    - Lexmark
      - Corporate video brief, 2000 (Box AF-R4)
      - Focus groups, 2000 (Box AF-R4)
      - Ink jet business, 2000 (Box AF-R4)
      - Intellitrack business imaging module, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - J110 effort, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Lexmark Plus brief, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Media, 1999-2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Mini Web brief, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Notes, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Scarecrow study, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Television, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - To Print in Color or Not…, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Wall Street Journal brief, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
      - Weber Group public relations, 2000 (Box AF-R5)
    - New Air/Project T
      - Competitive, 1998 (Box AF-R5)
      - Launch, 1998 (Box AF-R5)
    - Panasonic
      - Air purifier strategy, 1998 (Box AF-R6)
      - Brand image evaluation, 1998 (Box AF-R6)
      - Electric razor presentation, 1998 (Box AF-R6)
      - Fitch massage chair, 1998 (Box AF-R6)
      - Home products, 1998 (Box AF-R6)
      - Linear shaver, 1998 (Box AF-R6)
      - Men's shaver focus groups, 1998-2000, (4 folders) (Box AF-R6)
      - Power tools focus groups, 2000 (Box AF-R7)
      - Presentation, 1998 (Box AF-R7)
      - Public relations report, 1998 (Box AF-R7)
      - Research (Box AF-R7)
      - General, 1998 (Box AF-R7)
      - Men, 1998-2000 (Box AF-R7)
      - Women, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box AF-R7)
      - The Business of Advertising, 1998 (Box AF-R7)
      - Women's trimmers, 1998 (Box AF-R7)
    - Pilot Pen
      - General, 2000-2001, (3 folders) (Box AF-R8)
    - Prevention Magazine
      - Research, 1998 (Box AF-R8)
    - U.S. Tobacco
      - National Tobacco Incidence Study, 1998 (Box AF-R8)
- New Business Files, 1979-2001 and undated, (34 boxes)
  - AAMCO, 1997 (Box NB1)
  - AAR, 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box NB1)
  - A.B. Watley, 1997 (Box NB1)
  - Acclaim Entertainment, 1995-1997, (5 folders) (Box NB1)
  - Advertising Age agency report, 1993-1999, (2 folders) (Box NB2)
  - Adweek directories, 1993-1998, (2 folders) (Box NB2)
  - Adweek Report Card, 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box NB2)
  - Apparel lists, undated (Box NB2)
  - Au Bon Pain, 1997 (Box NB2)
  - Aventis Behring, 2000 (Box NB2)
  - Avon, 2000 (Box NB2)
  - Bed Bath & Beyond, 1998-1999 (Box NB3)
  - Boehringer Ingelheim, 1997 (Box NB3)
  - Budget Rent-a-Car, 1996 (Box NB3)
  - Burke Rehabilitation Hospital, 1985-1996 (Box NB3)
  - Business Week, 1992 (Box NB3)
  - Cabletron Systems, 1997, (2 folders) (Box NB3)
  - Canadian Club, 1996-1997, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box NB3)
  - Canadian Club, 1996-1997, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box NB4)
  - Carpet & Rug Institute, 1997 (Box NB4)
  - Carpet One, undated (Box NB4)
  - Case studies, 1993-1997 (Box NB4)
  - Chase Manhattan, 1999 (Box NB4)
  - Chemical Manufacturers Association (CMA), 1990 (Box NB4)
  - Church & Dwight, 1998 (Box NB4)
  - Coors, 1997 (Box NB4)
  - Creative samples, 1998 (Box NB4)
  - Current projects, 1996-1997 (Box NB4)
  - CVS, 1997 (Box NB5)
  - Directories, 1997 (Box NB5)
  - Dow Jones Telerate, 1996, (2 folders) (Box NB5)
  - Epson, 1997 (Box NB5)
  - Findlandia Vodka, 1996 (Box NB5)
  - Foster Grant, 1998 (Box NB5)
  - Four Seasons Hotels, 1998 (Box NB5)
  - General, 1980-1993, (1 of 4 folders) (Box NB5)
  - General, 1980-1993, (2-4 of 4 folders) (Box NB6)
  - GeoCities, 1998 (Box NB6)
  - Glaxo SmithKline (Relafen), 1996-1998 (Box NB6)
  - Go.com, 1999 (Box NB6)
  - GoJo/Purell, 1996 (Box NB6)
  - Grand Marnier competitive advertising, 1994-1995 (Box NB6)
  - Harper Collins, 1998 (Box NB6)
  - Health First, 1997 (Box NB7)
  - Health Insurance Plan (HIP USA), 1997, (2 folders) (Box NB7)
  - HomeRuns.com, 2000 (Box NB7)
  - Hardee's, 1997 (Box NB7)
  - Jack Daniels, 2000 (Box NB7)
  - Jones-Lundin Associates, 1996 (Box NB7)
  - LaLigue North America, 1999 (Box NB7)
  - Leads
    - Active, 1994-1995 (Box NB7)
    - Current, 1995-1996 (Box NB7)
    - Kevin O'Neill leads, 1996-1997 (Box NB8)
    - Ronald Fierman leads, 1996 (Box NB8)
    - Wilder Baker leads, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box NB8)
  - Lee Jeans, 1999 (Box NB8)
  - Lehn & Fink--New product ideas, 1979 (Box NB8)
  - Lindt & Sprüngli, 2001 (Box NB8)
  - Loew's Hotels, 1996 (Box NB8)
  - Long John Silver's, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box NB8)
  - Luzianne Tea, 1997, (2 folders) (Box NB8)
  - MacGregor Golf, 1999 (Box NB8)
  - Madison Square Garden Network (MSG), 1997 and undated, (1 of 2 folders) (Box NB8)
  - Madison Square Garden Network (MSG), 1997 and undated, (2 of 2 folders) (Box NB9)
  - Memoranda, 1993 (Box NB9)
  - MFS Asset Management, 1994-1995 (Box NB9)
  - Mitsubishi, 1997 (Box NB9)
  - Nancy Kieffer files, 1991-1992, (3 folders) (Box NB9)
  - Neuberger Berman, 2000 (Box NB9)
  - New Business advertisement samples, undated (Box NB10)
  - New York business mailing, Walk-through booklet, 1979 (Box NB10)
  - New York Hospital, 1996-1998 (Box NB10)
  - New York Life, undated (Box NB10)
  - Northern Trust, 2000 (Box NB10)
  - Ogilvie Home Permanent, 1997 (Box NB10)
  - Panasonic, 1997-1999, (2 folders) (Box NB10)
  - Prodigy, 1997, (2 folders) (Box NB10)
  - Questionnaire responses, 1985-1987, (7 folders) (Box NB11)
  - Rand McNally, 1997-2000 (Box NB12)
  - Red Book, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box NB12)
  - Reily Foods, 1997 (Box NB12)
  - Research (Box NB12)
  - Beer, 1995-1997, (2 folders) (Box NB12)
  - Business-to-Business, 1995 (Box NB12)
  - Edible dry-packed food client, undated (Box NB12)
  - Mega-brands, 1992 (Box NB12)
  - Qualitative creative thinking, 1997 (Box NB12)
  - Technology, 1996 (Box NB12)
  - Wine/Liquor, 1999 (Box NB12)
  - Selfcare, 1997 (Box NB13)
  - SNET, 1996-1997, (7 folders) (Box NB13)
  - SNET/Teligent, 1997 (Box NB14)
  - Status reports, 1993-1997 (Box NB14)
  - Teligent, 1997 (Box NB14)
  - Tennis Industry Association, 1995, (3 folders) (Box NB14)
  - T. Rowe Price, 2000 (Box NB14)
  - Tumi, 1997-2000 (Box NB14)
  - U.S. Trust, 2000 (Box NB14)
  - USA Network, 1996 (Box NB14)
  - Warburg Pincus, 2000 (Box NB14)
  - Warwick Advertising self-promotion, 1982 (Box NB14)
  - Warwick Baker O'Neill credentials, 1998 (Box NB14)
  - Restricted Files
    - 1-800 Flowers, 1999 (Box NB-R1)
    - AAA (American Automobile Association), 1998 (Box NB-R1)
    - AAMCO, 2000 (Box NB-R1)
    - AAR, 1998 (Box NB-R1)
    - Achenbaum Bogda, 1998 (Box NB-R1)
    - Administrative--Account experience, 1998 (Box NB-R1)
    - Adams Golf, 1999 (Box NB-R1)
    - Advertising Age agency report, 2000 (Box NB-R1)
    - Advertising Agency Search Service, 1998 (Box NB-R1)
    - Adweek Report Card, 2000 (Box NB-R1)
    - Agency credentials, 1999, (2 folders) (Box NB-R1)
    - AIG, 1999 (Box NB-R1)
    - Alberto-Culver, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box NB-R1)
    - Amerifit, 1999 (Box NB-R1)
    - AMTICO, 1998 (Box NB-R1)
    - Astra Pharmaceuticals (CrossCom), 1998, (2 folders) (Box NB-R1)
    - Autonation/Republic, 1999 (Box NB-R2)
    - Avid Technology, 1998-2000, (3 folders) (Box NB-R2)
    - Bacardi, 1998 (Box NB-R2)
    - Bacardi/DiSaronno, 1998, (4 folders) (Box NB-R2)
    - Bausch & Lomb, 1999, (3 folders) (Box NB-R3)
    - Bedford Group, 1998 (Box NB-R3)
    - Bermuda Tourism, 1998 (Box NB-R3)
    - Best Selections, 1999-2000, (6 folders) (Box NB-R3)
    - Bismark, 1999 (Box NB-R3)
    - Boston Beer, 1998 (Box NB-R3)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs, 1999, (1 of 3 folders) (Box NB-R3)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs, 1999, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box NB-R4)
    - Brandwise, 1999 (Box NB-R4)
    - Brown-Forman (Southern Comfort, Canadian Mist), `1996-1998 (Box NB-R4)
    - Business 2.02000 (Box NB-R4)
    - Budget Rent-a-Car, 2000 (Box NB-R4)
    - Cabletron Systems, 2001 (Box NB-R4)
    - Car Max, 1998 (Box NB-R4)
    - Car Temps, 1999 (Box NB-R4)
    - Cayman Islands, 2001 (Box NB-R4)
    - CFSB Direct, 2001 (Box NB-R4)
    - Clear Perspectives, 1999 (Box NB-R4)
    - Clorox, 1999 (Box NB-R4)
    - Computer Associates, 2000, (2 folders) (Box NB-R4)
    - Consultant mailings, 1998 (Box NB-R4)
    - Cooper Tire, 1999, (4 folders) (Box NB-R5)
    - Coty, 1999 (Box NB-R5)
    - Creative Selling Opportunities, 1998 (Box NB-R5)
    - Cross Pen, 2000 (Box NB-R5)
    - Dan Foss Group, 2001 (Box NB-R5)
    - Datek Online, 1999 (Box NB-R6)
    - Denny's, 2000 (Box NB-R6)
    - Direct-to-Consumer leads, 1998 (Box NB-R6)
    - Distilled Spirits Council, 2001 (Box NB-R6)
    - Eastman Kodak, 1998 (Box NB-R6)
    - EBJ Management Consultants, 1998 (Box NB-R6)
    - Eight O'Clock Coffee, 1998-1999, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box NB-R6)
    - Eight O'Clock Coffee, 1998-1999, (3 of 3 folders) (Box NB-R7)
    - Erie Insurance, 1999 (Box NB-R7)
    - ESC Medical Systems (Epitouch hair removal), 1998-2000, (4 folders) (Box NB-R7)
    - Etienne Aigner, 2000 (Box NB-R7)
    - Financial Times, 1998 (Box NB-R7)
    - Frank's Nursery & Crafts, 1998 (Box NB-R7)
    - Gallo, 1999 (Box NB-R7)
    - Geduldig & Ferguson, 1998 (Box NB-R7)
    - GeoCities, 1998 (Box NB-R7)
    - Gilbert Fairie, 1998 (Box NB-R8)
    - Godiva Chocolatier, 1998 (Box NB-R8)
    - Guinness Import, 1999 (Box NB-R8)
    - Hallmark Cards, 1998 (Box NB-R8)
    - Hanes, 2001 (Box NB-R8)
    - Hartz Mountain, 1998 (Box NB-R8)
    - Heinz Pet Products (9 Lives), 2001, (2 folders) (Box NB-R8)
    - Heritage Consumer Products, 1998 (Box NB-R8)
    - Hyperion, 2000 (Box NB-R8)
    - Iams, 1998-1999 (Box NB-R8)
    - Independent Insurance Agents of America (IIAA), 1999 (Box NB-R8)
    - International Paper, 1999 (Box NB-R8)
    - Interpartners, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box NB-R8)
    - Jan Apple, 1998 (Box NB-R9)
    - Jen's project (beer/wine), 1998 (Box NB-R9)
    - Jiffy Lube, 1999 (Box NB-R9)
    - Johnson & Johnson, 1999 (Box NB-R9)
    - Kevin O'Neill quote file, 1999 (Box NB-R9)
    - Kirin Beer, 1998 (Box NB-R9)
    - Knoll Pharmaceutical, 1998 (Box NB-R9)
    - Larry Weisberg, 1998 (Box NB-R9)
    - Lender's Bagels, 2000 (Box NB-R9)
    - Lenscrafters (Liquid Marketing), 1998-2000 (Box NB-R9)
    - Levi Strauss, 1999 (Box NB-R9)
    - Lexmark, 1999-2000, (2 folders) (Box NB-R9)
    - Liberty Mutual, 1998-2000, (2 folders) (Box NB-R9)
    - Lichtwer Pharma, 1998, (1 of 4 folders) (Box NB-R9)
    - Lichtwer Pharma, 1998, (2-4 of 4 folders) (Box NB-R10)
    - Long John Silver's, 2000 (Box NB-R10)
    - Lord, Abbott, 1999 (Box NB-R10)
    - Luxury goods, 1998 (Box NB-R10)
    - Madison Square Garden Network (MSG), 1998, (2 folders) (Box NB-R10)
    - Mailing database, 1998 (Box NB-R10)
    - Mark Goldstein, 1998 (Box NB-R10)
    - McBride & Associates, 1998 (Box NB-R10)
    - McDonald's, 1999 (Box NB-R10)
    - Merck/Vioxx, 1998-1999, (1-8 of 13 folders) (Box NB-R11)
    - Merck/Vioxx, 1998-1999, (9-13 of 13 folders) (Box NB-R12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box NB-R12)
    - Mohegan Sun, 2001 (Box NB-R12)
    - Morgan Anderson, 1998 (Box NB-R12)
    - MyFamily.com, 2000 (Box NB-R12)
    - National Committee for Employer Support of the Guard and Reserves (Ad Council campaign), 1998 (Box NB-R12)
    - National Oil Heat Research Alliance (NORA), 2001, (2 folders) (Box NB-R12)
    - Naturalizer Shoe, 1998 (Box NB-R13)
    - Neal Gilliat, 1998 (Box NB-R13)
    - NECO Alliance, 2000 (Box NB-R13)
    - Neuberger Berman, 2000 (Box NB-R13)
    - New Air, 1998 (Box NB-R13)
    - New business expenses, 1998 (Box NB-R13)
    - New Business Perspective, 1998 (Box NB-R13)
    - New business projects, 1999 (Box NB-R13)
    - New England Consulting Group, 1998 (Box NB-R13)
    - New York Life, 1999 (Box NB-R13)
    - Ocean Spray, 1999 (Box NB-R13)
    - Olsten, 1997-1999, (1-2 of 5 folders) (Box NB-R13)
    - Olsten, 1997-1999, (3-5 of 5 folders) (Box NB-R14)
    - Panasonic, 1998, (2 folders) (Box NB-R14)
    - Panasonic Blood Pressure Omnibus, 2000 (Box NB-R14)
    - Patak Spices, 1999 (Box NB-R14)
    - Paul Stuart, 2000 (Box NB-R14)
    - PetSmart.com, 1999 (Box NB-R14)
    - Pfizer (Zyrtek), 1999, (1-3 of 4 folders) (Box NB-R14)
    - Pfizer (Zyrtek), 1999, (4 of 4 folders) (Box NB-R15)
    - Pharmacia/Upjohn, 2000, (2 folders) (Box NB-R15)
    - Pile & Company, 1998 (Box NB-R15)
    - Pilot Pen, 2001, (2 folders) (Box NB-R15)
    - Playtex Apparel, 2001 (Box NB-R15)
    - Porsche, 1998 (Box NB-R15)
    - Prevention Magazine, 1998 (Box NB-R15)
    - Private Bank of Boston case study, 2000 (Box NB-R15)
    - Project binder, 1999, (2 folders) (Box NB-R15)
    - Raynal & Cie., 2001, (2 folders) (Box NB-R16)
    - Republic Bank of New York, 1999 (Box NB-R16)
    - R.N. Gold, 1998 (Box NB-R16)
    - Rojek Marketing Group, 1998 (Box NB-R16)
    - Russell Athletics, 2000 (Box NB-R16)
    - Sara Lee Coffee & Tea, 2000 (Box NB-R16)
    - Sara Lee Underwear, 2000 (Box NB-R16)
    - Schott Glas, 1998 (Box NB-R16)
    - Schiefflin & Somerset (Grand Marnier, DiSaronno), 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box NB-R16)
    - Seagram's, 1998 (Box NB-R17)
    - Serta, 1999 (Box NB-R17)
    - Skincare prospect, 1998 (Box NB-R17)
    - Small World.com, 2000, (3 folders) (Box NB-R17)
    - Smuckers, 1999 (Box NB-R17)
    - SNET, 2000 (Box NB-R17)
    - Status reports, 1998 (Box NB-R17)
    - Stride Rite/Keds, 1999 (Box NB-R17)
    - Stridex, 2000 (Box NB-R17)
    - Tear Drop Golf, 1998 (Box NB-R17)
    - Teleglobe, 2001 (Box NB-R17)
    - Teligent, 1997-1998 (Box NB-R17)
    - Thrifty Rent-a-Car, 1998 (Box NB-R17)
    - T.J. Maxx, 2000 (Box NB-R17)
    - Tourneau Inc., 1999 (Box NB-R17)
    - Toys R Us, 1998 (Box NB-R17)
    - Trammel Crow, 1998, (3 folders) (Box NB-R18)
    - Triton PCS, 1998-1999, (1-3 of 5 folders) (Box NB-R18)
    - Triton PCS, 1998-1999, (4-5 of 5 folders) (Box NB-R19)
    - True Link, 2000 (Box NB-R19)
    - Turn downs, 1999 (Box NB-R19)
    - Tupperware, 1999 (Box NB-R19)
    - United Distillers & Vintners, 1999 (Box NB-R19)
    - United Steelworkers of America (USWA), 1998 (Box NB-R19)
    - Value-priced consumer packaged goods prospect, 1998 (Box NB-R19)
    - Valvoline, 2001 (Box NB-R19)
    - Verizon Wireless, 2000 (Box NB-R19)
    - Vitamin Shoppe, 2000 (Box NB-R19)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1998 (Box NB-R19)
    - Wanamaker Associates, 1998 (Box NB-R19)
    - Waterworks, 1998 (Box NB-R19)
    - W.E. Hooper & Associates, 1998 (Box NB-R19)
    - Weight Watchers, 1998 (Box NB-R19)
    - Wood Coalition, 2000, (2 folders) (Box NB-R20)
    - Woolmark, 1998 (Box NB-R20)
    - WQXR-FM/WQEW-AM, 1998 (Box NB-R20)
    - Yankee Candle, 2001, (3 folders) (Box NB-R20)
- Proof Books and Creative Output, 1962-1999 and undated, (22 boxes)
  - Ad Council/American Mental Health Fund1986 (Box PB1)
  - American Home Foods (including Chef Boyardee)1993 (Box PB1)
  - Benjamin Moore1972-1988, (4 folders) (Box PB1)
  - Berio Olive Oil1981-1982, 1993 (Box PB2)
  - Burke Rehabilitation Hospital1997 (Box PB2)
  - Burlington Industries (Box PB2)
  - Draperies1981-1985 (Box PB2)
  - Corporate campaigns (Brown Lung, Jobs, Idealism)1976 (Box PB2)
  - Home furnishings and bed linens (including Laura Ashley)1979-1985 (Box PB2)
  - Sandel, sportswear fabrics, Ultrex1977-1987 (Box PB2)
  - Television storyboards1979-1986 (Box PB2)
  - BVD Underwear1988-1998, (2 folders) (Box PB2)
  - Calvin Cooler1986 (Box PB2)
  - Century Shipping1985 (Box PB3)
  - Children's Book of the Month1993 (Box PB3)
  - Coty (Emeraude, Stetson)1982-1989 (Box PB3)
  - CPC International (Box PB3)
  - H-O Cereals1977-1983 (Box PB3)
  - Knorr1984-1997, (2 folders) (Box PB3)
  - Rit Dye1979-1994, (2 folders) (Box PB3)
  - Crafted With Pride1984-1996, (3 folders) (Box PB4)
  - Crossland Mortgage 1987-1990 (Box PB4)
  - d-Con1984-1989 (Box PB4)
  - Drake America1980 (Box PB4)
  - Economics Laboratory (Box PB5)
  - Cleaning products (including Clean & Smooth, Dip-It, Matey Fun Bath, Mildew's Gone, Scrub Free, Stain-Away, Star Coffee Filters)1973-1983 (Box PB5)
  - Electrasol1965-1983, (3 folders) (Box PB5)
  - Lime-Away1972-1978 (Box PB5)
  - Fiber, Fabric, and Apparel Coalition for Trade1985 (Box PB6)
  - Fruit of the Loom1998 (Box PB6)
  - General Wine & Spirits (Eagle Rare bourbon, Boodle's gin)1984 (Box PB6)
  - Glenbrook Laboratories (Calcitrel, Campho-Phenique, Midol, Stri-Dex)1985-1988 (Box PB6)
  - Great British Foods1984-1987 (Box PB6)
  - HomeEquity (later PHH HomeEquity)1984-1997, (2 folders) (Box PB6)
  - House of Seagram1985-1986 (Box PB6)
  - Ilford1987-1988 (Box PB6)
  - Italica olive oil1988 (Box PB6)
  - J Nelson Prewitt (Dif, Soil-Off)1965-1967 (Box PB7)
  - Jockey1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box PB7)
  - King Cola, Slim Cola1979-1980 (Box PB7)
  - Kirk's Folly (Lynx jewelry)1983 (Box PB7)
  - Lehn and Fink (Box PB8)
  - Body-All1972-1976 (Box PB8)
  - Dorothy Gray1973-1975 (Box PB8)
  - Medi-Quik1972-1979 (Box PB8)
  - Ogilvie1973-1974 (Box PB8)
  - Stri-Dex1979-1988 (Box PB8)
  - Miscellaneous1990-1992 (Box PB8)
  - Marta Olives 1980 (Box PB9)
  - Maybelline1983-1984 (Box PB9)
  - Miami Project to Cure Paralysis/Marc Buoniconti Fund1987 (Box PB9)
  - Miscellaneous publications (clipping file, including Wall Street Journal, Chicago Tribune, Men's Journal, USA Today)1998 (Box PB9)
  - New England Journal of Medicine1999 (Box PB9)
  - Parade Magazine1979-1983, (3 folders) (Box PB9)
  - Parade Magazine1982-1996, (7 folders) (Box PB10)
  - Plough (Box PB11)
  - A+D Ointment, Chlor-Trimeton, Coricidin, Drixoral, Duofilm/Duoplant, Lotrimin1992-1996 (Box PB11)
  - Artra, Aspergum1978-1982 (Box PB11)
  - Coppertone (including For Faces Only, QT, Tan Care)1978-1988, (2 folders) (Box PB11)
  - Coppertone, Correctol1978-1982 (Box PB11)
  - Correctol1983-1998 (Box PB11)
  - Di-Gel, Duration, Feen-a-Mint1977-1978 (Box PB12)
  - Paas makeup kits, Regutol1982-1983 (Box PB12)
  - Shade, Stri-Dex, Super Shade1980-1990 (Box PB12)
  - St. Joseph's1983-1993 (Box PB12)
  - St. Joseph's, Sulfur-8, Duration1977-1982 (Box PB12)
  - Prince1981 (Box PB12)
  - Schumacher (Waverly, Contract)1987-1994, (5 folders) (Box PB13)
  - Securities Group1980-1981 (Box PB13)
  - Segura Viudas1986-1987 (Box PB13)
  - Seagram's 71962 -1971, (6 folders) (Box PB14)
  - Seagram's 7 Crown1971-1973, (7 folders) (Box PB15)
  - Seagram's 7 Crown1974-1975, (5 folders) (Box PB16)
  - Seagram's VO1978-1984, (6 folders) (Box PB17)
  - Smithsonian Magazine1974 -1983, (5 folders) (Box PB18)
  - Smithsonian Magazine1983-1989, (5 folders) (Box PB19)
  - Swarogem1995 (Box PB20)
  - TIE/Communications1983-1986, (3 folders) (Box PB20)
  - Tussy cosmetics1973 (Box PB20)
  - Van Munching (Amstel, Buckler, Heineken)1988-1993 (Box PB20)
  - West Point Pepperell1989-1990 (Box PB20)
  - Mounted advertisements 1998, (6 folders) (Box PB21)
  - Bulmer's, Magner's cider, undated (Box PB21)
  - Crafted with Pride1988-1989 (Box PB21)
  - Employer Support of the Guard and Reserve (ESGR)1990s (Box PB21)
  - Crafted with Pride photographs and ephemera (tags, labels, stickers, towels), undated (Box PB22)
  - Large format print advertisements (Box PB22)
  - BVD Underwear1998-1992 (Box PB22)
  - Crafted with Pride1988 (Box PB22)
  - Fruit of the Loom1998-1999 (Box PB22)
  - Parade Magazine (includes React youth magazine)1986-1998 (Box PB22)
  - Plough--Correctol1988-1989 (Box PB22)
- Large-Format Materials1931-1997 and undated, (11 boxes)
  - Accounts--Bausch & Lomb creative, 1996 (Box OV1)
  - Accounts--Crafted with Pride case history1989 (Box OV1)
  - Accounts--Crafted with Pride qualitative research, undated (Box OV1)
  - Accounts--DiSaronno focus group1998 (Box OV1)
  - Legal--Benjamin Moore contracts1972 (Box OV1)
  - Legal/Financial--Acquisition of stocks1979-1980 (Box OV1)
  - Legal/Financial--Incorporation and stock issue 1979-1980 (Box OV1)
  - Legal/Financial--Leases for 375 park Avenue1957-1981, (2 folders) (Box OV1)
  - Legal/Financial--Leases for Berkshire Hotel, 605 Park Avenue1962-1980 (Box OV1)
  - Research--Beer market questionnaire, undated (Box OV1)
  - Color Reference Guide, undated (Box OV2)
  - Duo Color Guide1955 (Box OV2)
  - Creative portfolio (includes Benjamin Moore, CPC International, Parade, Plough, Schumacher, U.S. Tobacco, Van Munching1990 (Box OV3)
  - Direct marketing/Business-to-business portfolio (Box OV3)
  - Benjamin Moore, Burlington, BVD, Century Shipping, Coldwell Banker1987 (Box OV3)
  - Crafted With Pride, Crossland Savings, Direct Travel, Equitable Invitational1986-1987 (Box OV3)
  - Gronich & Co., HomeEquity1987 (Box OV3)
  - Ilford/Ciba, Jockey1986-1988 (Box OV3)
  - Seagram1980-1985 (Box OV3)
  - Shady Brook Farms, U.S. Mortgage Corporation, undated (Box OV3)
  - Warwick Advertising/Warwick Plus1986-1988 (Box OV3)
  - Miscellaneous materials (Box OV4)
    - AAR Retail Questionnaire Response1996 (Box OV4)
    - Fast food service articles1996-1997 (Box OV4)
    - Feature on Warwick Baker & Fiore research on female consumers1995 (Box OV4)
    - Tomorrow newsletter, printed self-promotional material1983-1984 (Box OV4)
    - Warwick Welsh & Miller credentials bookcirca 1978 (Box OV4)
  - Press clippings
    - 1931 -1950, (7 folders) (Box OV5)
    - 1951-1954, (8 folders) (Box OV6)
    - 1957-1960, (6 folders) (Box OV7)
    - 1966-1969, (7 folders) (Box OV8)
    - 1968-1970, (5 folders) (Box OV9)
    - 1972-1984, (6 folders) (Box OV10)
  - Stocks
    - Stock certificates1966-1973 (Box OV11)
    - Warwick and Legler ledger1954-1972 (Box OV11)
    - Common stock1940-1961 (Box OV11)
    - Common stock1951-1952 (Box OV11)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1985-1998 and undated
  Restrictions on access: Original audiovisual materials are closed to patrons until a use copy can be produced.
  - America's Textiles: An Industry Fights Back. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV1)
  - Benjamin Moore--Word of Mouth. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:15 (Box AV1)
  - Beer review. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Bobbin Show/Miss America. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 7:06 (Box AV1)
  - Boys and Girls Club. Undated. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV1)
  - BRS Group--Shaving group 1.1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - BRS Group--Shaving group 2.1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - BRS Group--Shaving group 3.1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - BRS Group--Shaving group 4.1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - BRS Group--Used Cars group 1. 1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - BRS Group--Used Cars group 2. 1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Buying Pattern One-on-One tape 1. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Buying Pattern One-on-One tape 2. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Buying Pattern One-on-One tape 3. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Buying Pattern One-on-One tape 4. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Chicago--Debbie Tierro, Kathy Kelly. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Chicago--Kris Larabee. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Chicago--Sue Blank, Carol Hanson. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Chicago floater--Carol Ann Krugger, Chris Jones. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Chicago floater--Paula Borys, Ann Marie Langdon. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Chicago floater--Susan Hack, Katy Bonamarte, Sheila Prenergast. 1994. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV1)
  - Crafted with Pride--ATMI presentation. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV1)
  - Crafted with Pride--ATMI presentation. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV1)
  - Crafted with Pride--Bobbin Show. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV1)
  - Crafted with Pride--Bobbin Show. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV1)
  - Crafted with Pride--Cameo takes. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV1)
  - Crafted with Pride--Cameo with Sammy. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV1)
  - Crafted with Pride--Celebrities/People/Loretta Switt. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:15 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Crafted in USA logo. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Crate. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Crate/Line. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 2:55 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Crate/Line. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:55 (Box AV2)